# **Angel Ramirez**

### **Aspiring UI Designer and Developer**

#### **ABOUT**

Angel is a strong-believer of continuous learning and staying relevant in the ever-evolving job market. She has completed a Diploma in Web Development and Programming from Singapore Polytechnic and aspires to be a UI Designer and Developer. She has a Degree in Communication and has over 7 years of professional experience.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Manager at Gerson Lehrman Group - Singapore June 2016 – Present (4 years)

- Special assignment Tech Liaison for Southeast Asia.
  - Spearheads internal strategic implementation of new technology solutions that improve business efficiency and expert user experience.
  - Coordinates with the APAC tech liaison head, based in Hong Kong, on technology tests and roll-outs for the region.
- Head of Philippines Councils grow the expert network by onboarding and engaging key opinion leaders, C-level executives and high-profile experts from Fortune 500 companies, large MNCs, governments, unicorns start-ups among others.
- Mentor and coach new-joiners and interns. Foster an environment where individual team members hit their KPIs.
- Started as an Associate in 2016, promoted to Senior Associate in Jan 2018 and finally to Manager in Dec 2019.

# Business Development Executive at Gates PCM Integrated Services Pte. Ltd. - Singapore

#### March 2015 - June 2016 (1 year and 4 months)

• Achieved a "dream project" for the company - a landmark site which engages all of GPIS' services within just 2 months of employment with the company.

## TV Journalist at People's Television Network. - Philippines January 2013 – January 2015 (2 years)

- Covered major beats such as:
  - Senate of the Philippines (Upper Legislative House)
  - Department of Foreign Affairs
  - Department of Finance
- Live (on-camera) coverage of various events such as natural



#### **EDUCATION:**

# Diploma (Conversion) in Web and Programming

Singapore Polytechnic March 2020

#### Interaction Design for the Web

Lynda from LinkedIn Learning (Online Learning) March 2019

#### Data Analytics, Certificate

General Assembly, Singapore April 2018

#### Responsive Web Design

freeCodeCamp (Online learning) September 2018

# Bachelor of Arts in

#### Communication

Graduated with Academic Honours Miriam College, Philippines March 2013

#### **SKILLS:**

